"Hey, we found a bug"
and report it, so it can be fixed.
(Penny:)You mean like a beta test?
(Leonard:)Technically, this would be an alpha test.
(Leonard:)A beta test requires people that
weren't involved in the develop...
Seriously? Do I not get credit
for knowing beta test?
(Leonard:)No, you should. Absolutely.
That was me being pedantic.
And that's our first bug.
(Leonard:)You reported it, I can fix that.
See? This is good.
(Penny:)All right. Let's give it a shot.
(Leonard:)Great. You keep a list, I'll keep a list,
at some point, we'll exchange.
- Okay. Good night, Leonard.
- Night.
(Leonard:)Attaboy, Hofstadter.
Nothing gets the Iadies hotter
than software development analogies.
(Leonard:)- Hey, I'm back.
Cut.